OBJECTIVE: DATA ANALYST

Former Graphic Designer & Operations Manager transitioning into a **Data Analyst** role. Looking to take advantage of my skills in graphic design over 5 years of experience for more effective and efficient data visualizations and communications. **Key skills include:**

Data Visualization and Modeling

• Proficient in using Tableau for creating data visualizations and models.

Communication

 Skilled in creating visualization that displays the findings in a way that non-technical users can comprehend.

CERTIFICATIONS

• University of California, Irvine – Division of Continuing Education – Data Science Certificate (2021) (8 months, 150 hours of evaluated learning) (4.0 GPA)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Data Science: Tableau, Python, SQL, KNIME, RapidMiner and Excel.
- Graphic Design: Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign.

LINKS

- Portfolio Website Portfolio website with a brief introduction about myself.
- <u>Tableau Dashboard</u> Tableau Public dashboard that showcases my recent projects.
- GitHub GitHub repositories that showcases my other data science projects.

EXPERIENCE

IKEDA Japanese Dining

Huntington Beach, CA

2020 - 2021

- **Graphic Designer and Operations Manager**
- Coordinated employee work schedules and performed all administrative works.
- Implemented and executed all graphic design needs such as new menu design and advertisements.

WeGen Solar Inc.

Fullerton, CA 2015 – 2020

Graphic Designer and Operations Manager

- In charge of interconnection process for solar commercial and residential projects.
- Managed solar monitoring system maintenances for commercial solar projects and all residential customers.
- In charge of every graphic design work for marketing purposes (advertisements and sales support).

SuperCap Co.

Los Angeles, CA

Co-Founder and Online Marketing Manager

2014 – 2014

- Co-founded a hat retail company and performed as an online marketing manager.
- Increased sales by creating an official company website with WordPress and selling products online via company website and eBay.
- Raised brand awareness by advertising and managing online product campaigns.

CJ Entertainment America Inc.

Los Angeles, CA

Temporary Graphic Designer in Marketing Team

2013 - 2014

- Responsible for daily graphic design needs and video editing for Korean films and corporate events.
- Wrote newly released Asian film press kits and shared with US film media and critics.

EDUCATION

Purdue University, College of Technology

West Lafayette, IN

Bachelor of Science | Computer Graphics Technology

May 2013